{
    "id": "b3e1f3f2e70742cc86fa36310a011be1",
    "title": "Will, would, shall, should",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2db13fc9633c4f998fe242992c6817c5",
            "title": "Will, Would, Shall, Should",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You ..................... see that I am right.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "shall",
                        "should"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. I open the door?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Shall",
                        "Will",
                        "Would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which pen ………………….. I buy?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shall",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………… talk about nothing but movies.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………. sit for hours listening to the radio.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "shall"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That …………………. be the postman, I think.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "shall",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… you have tea?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will",
                        "Shall",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................... you lend me your scooter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will",
                        "Shall",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………. sit for hours talking to herself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You …………………. keep your promise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "should",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}